<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TechDiversity</string>

    <string name="conference">(Conference)</string>
    <string name="hackathon">(Hackathon)</string>
    <string name="fellowship">Fellowship</string>
    <string name="internship">(Internship)</string>
    <string name="research">(Research)</string>
    <string name="scholarship">(Scholarship)</string>

    <string name="code2040">Code2040 Fellowship</string>
    <string name="code2040_description">CODE2040\'s flagship program places top performing Black and
        Latino/a college level computer science students from around the country in an intensive
        summer career accelerator in the San Francisco Bay Area. Students intern at top tech
        companies and participate in a series of career building sessions on evenings and weekends.
    </string>

    <string name="app_closed">Application not open</string>
    <string name="more_info">More Info</string>
    <string name="apply">Apply</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>

    <string name="microsoft_ds3">Microsoft Research Data Science Summer School</string>
    <string name="microsoft_ds3_shortened">Microsoft DS3</string>
    <string name="deadline_apr15">Deadline: April 15, 2016</string>
    <string name="ds3_description">The Data Science Summer School (DS3) is an intensive,
        eight-week hands-on introduction to data science for college students in the
        New York City area. Each student receives a $5,000 stipend for participating in the program, as well
        as a laptop.
        DS3 includes both course work in data science and group research projects. The
        summer school is taught by leading scientists at Microsoft Research, and is held
        at the new Microsoft Research office in the heart of New York City.</string>

    <string name="eligibility_reqs">Eligibility</string>
    <string name="college_enrolled">- Must be currently enrolled in an undergradate program in the New York City area</string>
    <string name="cmpu_programming">- A familiarity with computer programming and/or statistics is helpful</string>
    <string name="international_allowed">- Open to international students</string>

    <string name="app_materials">Application Materials</string>
    <string name="personal_statement">- Personal Statement</string>
    <string name="transcript">- (Unofficial) Transcript</string>
    <string name="resume">- Resume/CV</string>
    <string name="references">- 2 Letters of Recommendation</string>

    <string name="buildium_scholarship">Buildium Women in Technology Scholarship</string>
    <string name="buildium_desc">The Women in Technology Scholarship is available to female students
        who are enrolled in a product design, interaction design, engineering, and computer science,
        or user experience design program. One $2,500 scholarship will be awarded each semester to
        a women who can say which female leader most inspires them to pursue their dreams,
        and why.</string>
    <string name="female_student">- Must be a female enrolled in an accredited undergraduate or
        graduate degree program in Product Design, Interaction Design, UX Design, or
        Computer Science.</string>
    <string name="age">- Must be 18 years of age or older and in good academic standing with their
        college or University</string>
    <string name="essay">- Essay, 1000 words or less, telling which female leader at a technology
        company inspires you, and why</string>
    <string name="how_submit">**All essays can be submitted to scholarship@buildium.com with a
        subject line of “Women in Technology Scholarship”</string>

    <string name="tapia_conference">ACM Richard Tapia Celebration of Diversity in Computing</string>
    <string name="tapia_conference_shortened">Tapia Comference</string>




    <string name="motto">Striving for more diversity in the technology industry!</string>

    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="join_now">New to TechDiversity? Join Now</string>

    <string name="save_for_later">Save for Later</string>
    <string name="not_interested">Not Interested</string>
</resources>
